<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>

        <!-- Report Action -->
        <record id="report_appointment_letter_direct" model="ir.actions.report">
            <field name="name">Appointment Letter</field>
            <field name="model">employee.letter</field>  <!-- ✅ correct model -->
            <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
            <field name="report_name">cmr_new_recruitments.report_appointment_letter_template_direct</field>
            <field name="report_file">cmr_new_recruitments.report_appointment_letter_template_direct</field>
            <field name="print_report_name">'Appointment_Letter_%s' % (object.name)</field>
        </record>


        <!-- Report Template -->
        <template id="report_appointment_letter_template_direct">
            <t t-name="cmr_new_recruitments.report_appointment_letter_template_direct">
                <t t-call="web.html_container">
                    <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                        <div class="page">
                            <p>26-12-2022</p>
                            <p>Visakhapatnam.</p>
                            <p>Emp :
                                <t t-esc="doc.name or ''"/>
                            </p>

                            <p>Dear<t t-esc="doc.employee_id or doc.name or 'Candidate'"/>,
                            </p>

                            <p>This is reference to your application and the subsequent interview you had with us. We
                                are pleased to appoint you as
                                <strong>
                                    <t t-esc="doc.designation_id.name or 'Assistant Manager'"/>
                                </strong>
                                in our business on the following terms and conditions of your appointment.
                            </p>

                            <h4>Appointment and Reporting</h4>

                            <p>
                                1.1 You are required to join the services of the company on or before
                                <strong>
                                    <t t-esc="doc.date_of_joining.strftime('%d-%m-%Y') if doc.date_of_joining else ''"/>
                                </strong>
                                .
                                If you fail to report to duty on or before the joining date, you will be deemed not to
                                have joined
                                the company and this appointment letter will be considered withdrawn/cancelled without
                                any further liability.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                1.2 At the time of joining, you are requested to furnish copies of your educational
                                qualifications,
                                testimonials, and a relieving letter from your previous organization. This offer is also
                                subject to
                                you not being under any contractual obligation that prevents you from accepting this
                                offer or
                                starting work on the date of joining.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                1.3 In case you do not submit the required documents within <strong>30 days</strong> from
                                your date of joining,
                                the company shall be constrained to hold back your salary until such documents are
                                furnished.
                            </p>


                            <h4>2. Initial Posting and Transfer</h4>

                            <p>
                                2.1 Your initial place of posting shall be at <strong>Vizag</strong>.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                2.2 You will be liable to transfer in such capacity as the company may from time to time
                                determine to any other location or department. In such case, you will be governed by the
                                terms and conditions of services applicable to the new assignment.
                            </p>


                            <h4>3. Probation</h4>

                            <p>
                                3.1 You will be on a probation period of <strong>6 months</strong> from the date of
                                joining, and your confirmation will be subject to satisfactory completion of the
                                probation period.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                3.2 During the probation period, your employment is terminable by either party by giving <strong>
                                15 days’ notice</strong>.
                            </p>


                            <h4>4. Confidential Information</h4>

                            <p>
                                4.1 During the course of your employment and by virtue of the position held by you, you
                                shall keep and maintain strict confidentiality of all information and data.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                4.2 Upon expiry or termination of your employment with the company, you must return and
                                surrender to your supervisor all such confidential information, including but not
                                limited to data, files, books, reports, and records.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                4.3 You shall not disclose any such information to the public or in any media, public
                                papers, or journals.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                4.4 You are required to adhere to and comply with the company’s information security
                                policy at all times.
                            </p>


                            <h4>5. Incentive</h4>

                            <p>
                                5.1 You will also participate in the company’s incentive plan as applicable to your
                                role. The plan will be communicated to you by your management.
                            </p>


                            <h4>6. Timing</h4>

                            <p>
                                6.1 Your work timings will be as per the Company rules pertaining to the stores to which
                                you are currently attached.
                            </p>

                            <h4>7. Termination</h4>

                            <p>
                                7.1 Your appointment and continued employment with the company is strictly based on
                                consistently delivering performance as per agreed parameters and business targets.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                7.2 <strong>Absenteeism:</strong> If you absent yourself without leave or remain absent
                                beyond the period of granted or extended leave, you shall be considered as having
                                voluntarily terminated your employment unless:
                            </p>
                            <ul>
                                <li>You return to work within 7 working days from the commencement of such absence;
                                    and
                                </li>
                                <li>You provide a satisfactory explanation to the Management for the absence.</li>
                                <li>If you are found medically unfit to continue the job, you may be terminated from
                                    employment.
                                </li>
                            </ul>

                            <p>
                                7.3 <strong>Harassment:</strong> The company considers harassment and discrimination of
                                any nature to be unacceptable behavior and it will not be tolerated under any
                                circumstance.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                7.4 Disciplinary action, including termination of employment, will be taken against
                                anyone found guilty of harassment or discrimination against a fellow employee.
                            </p>


                            <h4>8. Retirement / Notice Period</h4>

                            <p>
                                8.1 You will retire from the services of the Company upon attaining the age of 58 years
                                or such retirement age as may be decided by the Management.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                8.2 This contract of employment is terminable by either party with a 60 days’ (2 months)
                                notice period.
                            </p>

                            <p>
                                The company shall have the right to terminate your employment without notice if:
                            </p>
                            <ul>
                                <li>You become insolvent or bankrupt, or are charged with a criminal offence that is
                                    prejudicial to the interests of the company.
                                </li>
                                <li>You commit any material breach of your duties and responsibilities under this
                                    contract.
                                </li>
                                <li>You are involved in harassment at the workplace.</li>
                                <li>You are found in violation of any of your obligations under the general terms and
                                    conditions of employment and the Code of Conduct as outlined in Annexure 1. The
                                    company’s opinion in such matters shall be final and binding.
                                </li>
                            </ul>

                            <h4>ANNEXURE 1: List of Misconduct</h4>

                            <p>Misconduct includes but is not limited to:</p>
                            <ol>
                                <li>Wilful insubordination or disobedience, whether alone or with others, to any lawful
                                    and reasonable order of the superior, including refusal to accept transfer.
                                </li>
                                <li>Theft, fraud, or dishonesty in connection with the company’s business or property.
                                </li>
                                <li>Wilful damage to or causing loss of goods or property.</li>
                                <li>Taking or giving bribe or commission for purchases/contracts made on behalf of the
                                    company.
                                </li>
                                <li>Remaining absent without information for more than 7 consecutive working days.</li>
                                <li>Habitual late attendance, leaving the workplace early, or being absent from the
                                    place of work without permission.
                                </li>
                                <li>Entering or remaining within the company premises except on duty or without
                                    authorization.
                                </li>
                                <li>Riotous behavior during working hours or any act subversive of discipline.</li>
                                <li>Negligence or neglect of work.</li>
                                <li>Refusal to work regular office hours while on the premises or disrupting
                                    co-workers.
                                </li>
                                <li>Engaging in private work or trade within the company premises or holding other
                                    employment for profit without written permission from the company.
                                </li>
                                <li>Displaying or distributing within the company premises any bills, pamphlets,
                                    placards, posters, or banners.
                                </li>
                                <li>Disclosing any confidential information obtained during the course of employment
                                    without authorization.
                                </li>
                                <li>Reporting to work under the influence of liquor.</li>
                                <li>Conviction by a court of law for any criminal offence involving moral turpitude.
                                </li>
                                <li>Quarrelling, fighting, or using abusive language within company premises.</li>
                                <li>Misbehaving with customers or contractors of the company.</li>
                                <li>Engaging in sexual harassment of any employee during or outside working hours.
                                    Sexual harassment includes:
                                    <ul>
                                        <li>Physical contact and advances</li>
                                        <li>Demand or request for sexual favours</li>
                                        <li>Sexually colored remarks</li>
                                        <li>Unwelcome physical, verbal or non-verbal conduct of a sexual nature causing
                                            annoyance to co-workers, vendors, or customers
                                        </li>
                                    </ul>
                                </li>
                            </ol>

                            <p>The company may revise the terms and conditions from time to time in its best interest.
                            </p>

                            <p>We look forward to your joining and wish you a rewarding and successful career with us.
                            </p>

                            <br/>
                            <p>
                                <strong>Authorised Signatory</strong>
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                <strong>CMR Textiles And Jewellers Private Limited</strong>
                            </p>

                            <br/>
                            <br/>
                            <h4>Acknowledgement and Acceptance</h4>
                            <p>
                                I have read and understood all the terms and conditions relating to my
                                appointment/employment and declare that I hereby unconditionally and irrevocably accept
                                the same.
                            </p>
                            <p>I hereby confirm joining the services of the company on: ____________________________</p>
                            <p>Name: __________________________ Signature: __________________________ Date:
                                __________________________
                            </p>


                            <p style="page-break-before:always;"></p>
                            <h4>SALARY BREAKDOWN</h4>
                            <table class="table table-sm table-bordered" style="width:100%; border-collapse: collapse;"
                                   border="1">
                                <thead>
                                    <tr style="background-color: #f0f0f0;">
                                        <th style="padding: 6px;">Component</th>
                                        <th style="padding: 6px;">Per Annum (₹)</th>
                                        <th style="padding: 6px;">Per Month (₹)</th>
                                    </tr>
                                </thead>
                                <tbody>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">CTC</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.ctc" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.ctc_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">Basic</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.basic" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.basic_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">HRA</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.hra" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.hra_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">Other Allowance</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.other_allowance" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.other_allowance_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">PF</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.pf" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.pf_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">PT</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.pt" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.pt_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">Net Take Home</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.net_take_home" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.net_take_home_m" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">Family Insurance</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.family_insurance" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td style="text-align: center; padding: 6px;">-</td>
                                    </tr>
                                    <tr>
                                        <td style="padding: 6px;">Bonus</td>
                                        <td t-esc="doc.bonus" style="text-align: right; padding: 6px;"/>
                                        <td style="text-align: center; padding: 6px;">-</td>
                                    </tr>
                                </tbody>
                            </table>


                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </t>
        </template>

    </data>
</odoo>
